Like you said, like you've been woke since you came out the womb into a cradle of wokeness.
Before they called it woke.
Yes, before they called it simply just like we like we're fighting for rights.
It was black power.
But I don't think we have black power in the same way anymore.
I think you are right.
Somewhere along the line, black power became synonymous with black financial success.
As people begin to see more black millionaires, then they thought or figure, hey, we've made it.
And that's it's not true.
It couldn't be further from the truth.
Right.
Because in all aspects of black life, people are dealing with oppression.
It might not look like bloodshed on your clothes, but it looks like being blocked from boardrooms.
It looks like not being able to get banks, not being able to get insurance in a new community where you bought a home.
It looks like being profiled on the streets.
It looks like worrying about your children at every second because you're scared to even let them go like to the basketball court.
Right.